Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Long have I awaited this moment, human filth.
こだいおう
古代王
この時を待ちわびたぞ 人間ども一
With the Subterranean
and Deep Sea kings gone,
しん力ヽいおう
も深海王も亡き今一
ち亡いおう
the Terror Lizard Clan can at last
reclaim rulership of the Earth!
きようりゆうぞく
我ら恐竜族が
再び この星を支配曹る
Now leading target towards point Bravo.
職員ー  現在 対象を 巳地点に誘導中
⑭パイ口ツ 卜了解 ! _
Roger.
We are inbound and on schedule.
メガネ職員
こちらも予定航路を飛行中
We'll be on top of Bravo shortly.
まもなボイン卜に到着しま萱
夕ツマキ フン
UNPARALLELED PERIL
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
And who are you?
古代王 何者だ お前は
立巳
信
憎
Hello? What is it?
夕ツマキ もしもし 何? 一
What do you mean, come back?!
はあ!? 戻れつ亡何よ!
You're the one who said some weirdo monster
had awoken and flew me out here!
変なのが目を覚ま萱力`らつて
ここに連れ亡きたのは
そつちでしよ!
Weirdo...
変なの… だと ?
That's right.
タツマキええ そう
ちょうどこれ力ヽら始めるとこ
I was just about to start.
Listen well! I am the Ancient King.
いい力` 我は古イ旺
As ruler of the dinosaurs
who once ruled this planet,
力ヽつ亡この星を支配し亡いた
夕ツマキヤバいって何よ!
"Trouble?" So what?
恐竜たちの長にして
夕ツマキそんなの私 関係ないわ!
It's not my problem.
Hey, shut it!
I stand above all other lifeforms.
うるさいわね 今 電話中なの!
分力ヽらないの!?
Can't you see I'm on the phone here?!
つた 何なのよ
I'm so tired of this.
Who's he think he is, ordering people about?
人をアゴで使つ 亡 何様よ
Are you done?
終わつたの力`?
夕ツマキ
何そのアゴ 威嚇のつもり?一
い力`
What's with the chin?
Trying to be scary?
Should I be intimidated?
それで怖がる と力`思つ 亡んの ?
Act brave while you still can, little runt.
粋力ヾつていられるのも今のうちだぞ
チビ人間
ん~!
チビとは何よ 失礼ね!
Runt?! How dare you!
でやあああ !
ほう 少しはやるようだな
Ah, so you aren't helpless!
But if you intend to destroy me,
a giant meteor is about the only way.
だが 我らを滅ぼしたければ
いんせき
隕石でも持つてくる以外に
方法はない
そう じやあ そう萱るわ
Fine. I'll do that then.
ハツ 笑わせる
Don't make me laugh.
How about another 300 million year nap?
夕ツマキ
もう3億年ほど眠つ亡れば?
りゆうすいがんさいけん
シ丿しバ一フアングヽ
Fist of Flowing Water, Crushed Rock.
まあ こんな風じや
It goes something like that.
Want to try?
どうじや やつてみん力`?
You both look like quick learners.
2人とも勘が良さそうだ力`ら
I bet you'll get the hang of it in no time.
曹ぐに身につけることが
できる力ヽもしれんぞ
This is the cool thing you
said you wanted to show us?
サイ夕マ
面白いもん見せてくれるつつ一力ヽら
わざわざ来たのに勧誘かよ
A sales pitch?
興味ね一よ
ジ工ノス お前やつとけ
I'll pass.
You do it, Genos.
No, I will pass too.
ジ工 ノス いや 俺も遠慮しま萱
What I seek is not the art of self-defense,
but absolute destructive power.
俺が求めるのは護身術ではなく
絶対的な破壊力で萱
You punks!
チヤランコ貴様ら!
流水岩砕拳を惠弄曹る力ヽ!
ぐろう
You dare mock our fighting style?!
I, Charanko, the top disciple, challenge you—
一番弟子チヤランコ 参る!
ぐえツ!
I give up!
ま・ まいつた
Is he really your best?
本当に一番弟子力`?
Yeah...
お前の道場は実力者揃いと
聞いていたんだが
I heard your dojo was full of skilled fighters.
はあ…
弟子のー 人が暴れおつての
Well, one of my disciples went wild.
実力派の弟子たちを
全て再起不能にしてしまったせいで
He beat my most skilled students
so badly they're all out of commission.
他の門下生も
恐れ亡辞め亡しもうたわ
The rest got scared and quit.
そいつ強いの力`? 名前は?
He's that strong?
What's his name?
Garo...
力`口ウ・‥
当時 一番弟子じや つ たが
He was my top disciple at the time,
but I gave him a good beating and expelled him.
ワシがボコボコにして
破門にしてやったわ
You must pack a punch, old man.
ジイサン 強いんだな
Hey! This is the famed hero "Silverfang,"
貴様! あのヒ一ロ一
シ丿しバ一フアング だぞ一
S級ヒ一口一ランキング3位 ! _
the 3rd ranked S-class hero.
In combat, he toys with opponents, flowing like water,
then delivers a blow like a raging river smashing huge rocks!
ほんろう
流水の動きで相手を翻弄し一
激流のごとき一撃をもつ亡
巨石をも粉砕曹る武術の達人!
A master of martial arts!
You only became a hero recently, right?
お前なんて 最近 ヒ一口一に
なつたば力ヽりのヒヨッコじゃない力ヽ
You'll regret taking Master Bang lightly!
バング先生をナメ亡ると
痛い目にあうぞ!
Enough, Charanko!
シ丿しバ一フアング よせ チヤランコ!
Do not disgrace us.
恥を力`力`せるな
Saitama is many times stronger than me.
ワシよりサイタマ君のほうが
何倍も強いわ!
Master, you can't be serious...
ちよ… 先生 ご冗談を…
職員2 シ丿しバ一フアング様 ! _
Mr. Silverfang!
The Association sent me.
ヒ一口一協会の者で萱 !
この度 S級ヒ一口一に
非常招集がかけられました!
An emergency summons has
been issued to all S-class heroes!
協会本部まで御足労願いま萱 !
Please come to Association Headquarters.
Oh! Is that you, Mr. Genos?
やや! そこにいるのは
ジェノス様で曹ね?一
S級は全員集合せよとのことで曹ので
ジェノス様も来亡いただきま曹!
Since all S-class heroes have been
summoned, please come as well.
レベ丿し竜が来た力` ?
Is it threat level Dragon?
Here we go...
チヤランコ 留守を頼むぞ
Charanko, look after the dojo.
Be careful, Master!
お気をつけて !
If all the S-class heroes are being summoned,
they may need your help too, Master.
S級が呼ばれるということは
先生の力も必要になるかもしれません
一緒に来てれま萱力`?
Will you come?
いいぜ 暇だ力`ら
I will… since I've got nothing to do.
CITY A – HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
Oh, it's Silverfang!
ア卜三ッ宴闇`
おお シルバ一フ ア ング!
It's been a while, Atomic Samurai.
ざむらい
久し振りじゃな ア卜三ック侍
I knew you'd come.
お前は来ると思つ亡いたぞ
And this is the cyborg Genos and...
あとはサイボ一グジ工ノスと…
Hm? Who's this?
ん ? ー人知らんのがいるな
彼は巳級のサイ夕マ君じゃ
This is the B-class hero Saitama.
いずれS級上位になる逸材だし
His exceptional talent will one day place him
atop Class S, I'm sure, so we asked him to come.
連れてきても問題はなガろう
Hi, middle-aged hero dude!
オツサンもヒ一口一なんだな
Put 'er there!
よろし!
No handshakes.
I acknowledge only the strong.
握手はせんぞ
俺は強者しか認めねぇ
Once you've climbed up to Class S,
I'll greet you properly.
お前力ヾここまで上力ヾつてきた時は
改めて挨拶をし亡やる
それに俺は
オツサンという歳じやねえ
Besides, I'm not middle-aged yet.
I'm only thirty-seven.
まだ37だ
サイ夕マ
37つ亡 オツサンじゃないの力ヽ
知らな力ヽった>
Thirty-seven isn't middle-aged?
I had no idea…
夕ツマキちょっと誰よ!
巳級の雑魚なんて連れてきたの
Hey, who brought a B-class nobody along?
私たちに対して
失礼だと力ヽ思わないの?
Don't you think it's beneath us?
And even if you were invited,
a polite person would decline. The nerve!
呼ばれ亡も普通来る力ヽしら?
どういう神経してんの?一
I bet you're only here for some creepy reason
like getting close to us S-class heroes.
S級とお近づきになりたいと力ヽ
浅い者えで ここに来たんでしよ
You disgust me.
消えて !
不愉快 !
Get out.
What's with this sassy, lost child?
サイ夕マ
何だ この生意気な… 迷子?
それはS級2位のタツマキで萱ね
That is Tornado. Rank 2, S Class.
What do you mean "that"?
I'm a person, you know!
それつ亡何よ! 物みたいに! プイッ
ジェノス超自然的な攻撃で一
She defeats monsters with her psychic powers.
怪人を倒萱 俗にいう工スパ一で萱
She is an Esper.
Oh yeah?
もう大体集まつてるようで萱一
It seems everyone's assembled.
We should join them.
席につきましよう
あ・ ちよつと! 無視萱る気?
Hey...
Stop ignoring me!
CLASS S, RANK 17
CO-CO CONVICT
Maybe this will be my chance
to get closer to Genos...
ぶりぶりプリズナー
これを機にー
ジ工ノスちやんと
仲良<なりたい
CLASS S, RANK 16
GENOS
ジ工ノス
よほどの
_大事なのかー
It must be serious.
Almost everyone is here.
ほとんどが
出席し亡いる
CLASS S, RANK 15
METAL BAT
きんぞ<、
金属バツ卜
鬼でも竜でも俺はいけるぜえ
Demon or Dragon, bring it on!
CLASS S, RANK 14
TANK-TOP MASTER
Saitama? The name rings a bell...
タンク卜ップマスター
サイタマ? 何処かで
聞いた名だな
CLASS S, RANK 13
FLASHY FLASH
CLASS S, RANK 12
WATCHDOG MAN
Somebody farted.
ばんブん
番犬マン
誰か屁こいたな
CLASS S, RANK 11
SUPERALLOY BLACKLUSTER
They're all checking out my guns.
ク口ビ力リ
みんながオレの肉体を
見亡いるー
見亡いる
Hell yeah!
CLASS S, RANK 10
PIG GOD
CLASS S, RANK 9
DRIVE KNIGHT
CLASS S, RANK 8
ZOMBIEMAN
ゾンビマン
こいつら
協調性なさそうだなー
No one looks particularly enthusiastic.
And does that pig ever stop eating?
あと あのブ夕は
いつまで食つ亡んだよ
キングの鼓動
CLASS S, RANK 7
KING
CLASS S, RANK 6
METAL KNIGHT
ABSENT
CLASS S, RANK 5
CHILD EMPEROR
謹謡
あれ またー位の人
来亡ないんだー
Rank 1's a no show again?
I was hoping to see him.
会いたかつたのに
CLASS S, RANK 4
ATOMIC SAMURAI
Is Silverfang going to take
those youngsters on as students?
ア卜三ツク侍
奴ー
あの若僧に
武術を教える気か?
CLASS S, RANK 3
SILVERFANG
Well, why are we all here?
んで 今日は
何の集まりなんじゃ
CLASS S, RANK 2
TERRIBLE TORNADO
知らないわよ!
Who knows?
I had to drop everything and then
they kept me waiting for two hours.
こっちは急に呼び戻され亡
2時間も待たされ亡るのよ
CLASS S, RANK 1
BLAST
ABSENT
CLASS B, RANK 63
SAITAMA
Can I have some tea?
お茶もらえる?
シツチ 萱まない 遅なつた一
My apologies for being late.
メ夕丿しナイ卜とブラス卜は
居場所がわ力ヽらず一
We do not know the whereabouts of
Metal Knight or Blast, nor can we reach them.
連絡もとれない状況だ一
No sense waiting any longer,
so let's begin this emergency meeting.
これ以上待っても 萱力ヾあ力ヽないので
緊急集会を始める
You can call me Sitch.
I'm with the Association. I will be briefing you.
私は今回の説明役を任された
ヒ一ロ一協会のシツチだ
Let's get right down to brass tacks.
早速 本題に入らせ亡いただこう一
You heroes are here because
you're the best of the best.
ヒ一口一界の頂点に立つ君たちに
集まってもらつたのは他でもない
And now...
We're asking you to save the Earth!
今回は地球を守つていただきたい!
However, even with your S-class skills,
there is no guarantee of survival.
し力ヽし 今回ば力ヽりは
超人ぞろいのS級メンバ一でも一
命を落と萱ガもしれん
逃げるのも勇気だ
Walking away also takes courage.
今なら 辞退しても
S級に籍だけは残し亡やる一
Should you choose to do so now,
you will retain your S-class status.
But those who stay and hear me out
will not be allowed to walk away.
だ力ヾ 今力ヽら言う話を聞いた者は
逃力ヾ曹わけにはい力ヽなくなる一
You will be confined here until the incident
is over in order to avoid a general panic.
事が終わるまで
こちらのほうで軟禁させてもらう一
混乱は避けたいのだ
Are you all willing to hear this?
みんな 話を聞覚悟はいいか ?
Whatever's going on,
金属バツ 卜 その話
it better be worth calling all of us here.
マジで俺たちを集めるだけの
内容なんだろうな オイ
I skipped out on my little
sister's piano recital for this.
こっちは妹の大事なビアノの演奏会を
抜け出して来たんだ
If it's a load of crap,
大したことねえ話だつたら
I'm gonna tear this whole building apart.
この本立
ロBをぶつ
壊曹ぞ
コラー
タツマキフン そんな棒きれで
できるわけないじゃない
Like you could do that with that skinny stick.
Yeah?
あ? 亡めえのク丿しク丿し頭
力ヽち割つてやろう力ヽ?
How 'bout I bust your head open instead?
If you think you can, go on and try, pillbug head!
やれるもんならやつ亡みなさいよ!
ダンゴムシ頭!
金属バッ 卜んだとお!
フラッシュさつさと用件を話せ
What was that?!
Hurry up and get on with it.
Otherwise Mr. Pompadour here is going to die.
でなければ このリ一ゼン卜が
死ぬことになるぞ
金属バッ 卜おいへアビン 亡めえ
女の味方力ヽ コラ?
Hey, bobby pin, you siding with the girl?
The great seer, Madame Shibabawa, is dead!
シッチ大予言者 シババワ様が
亡<なられた
Shibabawa?
ゾンビマンあのシババワ力ヾ?
殺されたの力ヽ?
Was she killed?
No.
メガネ職員
いえ 半年先までの未来を
占っていたところ
While looking into the future
for the next six months,
she became agitated and had a coughing fit.
気が動転 したの力`息が荒 な り
She popped a cough drop in
her mouth and ended up choking on it.
咳力ヾ出て のど飴を口に入れたら
そのまま のどに詰まらせ亡…
I get it!
ク口ビ力リなるほど
So we have to figure out how to prevent
disasters without the help of predictions.
今後は未来予想なしで
災害対策をしなければならない
That's the focus of this meeting.
それが今回の話の核だな
No.
獅
Madame Shibabawa has only been
able to predict a handful of disasters.
シババワ様は いつも
ご一部の災害しか予言できな力`つ た
Excuse me!
萱んません
ちよつと そこの人
Hey, you there.
シババワ様つ亡誰? ヒ一口一?
Who's this Shibabawa?
A hero?
You don't know?
知らないの力`?一
予言者だよ 大予言者一
She was a seer. A great one at that.
She correctly predicted earthquakes
and monster attacks.
地震と力ヽ怪人の来るタイ三ングを
ビタリと当亡る
ヒゲ 職員
シババワ様の予言なしでも
乗り越えてきた窮地は沢山ありま曹
We've gotten through many crises
without Madame Shibabawa's predictions.
But even so, we provided a bodyguard
and gave her special treatment.
それでも我々が身辺を警護し
特別扱いしていたのは…
ああ その予言が
ー。。%的中曹る力ヽらだ
Yes, because her few predictions
were 100% accurate.
The crux of the problem, though,
is her last, greatest prophecy.
問題の核となるのは
シババワ様が
最後に遺した大予言文
Even as she choked on that final cough drop,
she managed to leave this note.
のど飴を詰まらせながらも
害き残し亡くださった
の小さなメモ一
」
It is a prophecy that will
absolutely come to pass.
ー。。%訪れる未来が
ここにある
Here it is!
これだ!
Can you read it?
読める力`?
Th-The earth...
ち… 地球が
...is in trouble?!
ヤバい!?
THE EARTH.....
IS IN TROUBLE
童帝 何それ だらないなあ
What? That's so dumb.
Can I go? I have cram school.
ボク 塾ある力`ら 帰つていい力`な ?
どう亡い
童帝君は天才少年と聞い乙いたが
I know you are a prodigy, Child Emperor,
but if you cannot grasp the danger,
it reveals how immature you still are.
この危機を認識できないようでは
所詮 お子様と言わざるをえないぞ
しよせん
What'd you say?!
何だと蝿
Listen up!
いい力`い よ聞きたまえ
シババワ様の予言は
ー。。%当たる ! 一
Madame Shibabawa's predictions
are 100% accurate!
She has predicted many
catastrophes in the past.
そし亡 これまでも
い<つもの大災害を予言してきた一
その中には多くの命を奪う
結果となつたものもある一
A few of them resulted
in the loss of countless lives.
But not once did Madame Shibabawa
use the word "trouble."
し力ヽし シババワ様が
ヤバい と表現したことは一
今まで一度もな力`つた一
This will be something more dangerous
than a Dragon-level catastrophe or monster.
大災害や竜レベルの怪人が
顛来曹るよりも ヤバい こと力ヾ一
起きようとし亡いるのだ
And it will occur in the next six months!
それもこの半年以内に !
キングの鼓動
番犬マン
分力ヽつたけど 半年以内じゃ
いつ来る力ヽ分力ヽらないね
Okay, but we've no idea when
in the next six months.
Yeah, hard to plan for that.
ああ 対策の立てようがない
確力`に そのとおり だ
You are correct.
But I want you all to be ready
for a fight in the next six months.
だ力ヾし力ヽし 半年以内に
戦う覚悟はしておいてくれ!
In the next six months means...
サイ夕マ 半年以内つ亡ことは
明日力ヽもしれないし
今日力ヽもしれないな
it could be tomorrow, or even today.
う… そのとおりだが
お前は誰だ?
That's true. Who are you, anyway?
Good thing I'm here.
来亡良力`つた
ク口ビ力リお?
The building is under attack!
この建物が攻撃されてる !
そんな馬鹿な! ` `
ここはヒ一口一協会本部だぞ
That's impossible!
This is the Hero Association HQ!
人々の悲嗚
てん<う
雷はあ~ な力ヽな力ヽ
頑丈な建造物じゃないか一
A formidable fortress, to be sure!
うふわははははは 攻め込む力`
Time to attack.
Hawk, Eagle, Falcon, Kite!
ホ一ク ! イ一グ丿し!
ファ丿しコン! 力イ卜!
Yar!
一同 おおつ !
Wipe out these so-called heroes
and the land will be ours!
ヒ一口一とやらを誰鵠曹れば
地上はわしらのものだ!
一気にいただとしよう
We will dive straight in!
亡ん<うおう
この天空王についてこい!
Follow me, the Sky King!
Father... Above us...
力イ卜オヤジ… 上だ一
Escape...
逃げろ…
この天空王を
まるで虫のごとく…
Me, the Sky King,
killed like some worthless insect.
Who could have—
イ可も・‥
What was that?
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿し ドー 何だ 今の
Who knows?
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しド2分力`らん
It flew, so we killed it.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しド3
飛んでた力ヽら殺した
That is good.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しド4 いいと思うよ
Duty, to protect ship.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しド5船 守る 役目
⑭アナウンス
非常用電源システムを起動しま曹
Emergency power activated.
What was that?
シ ツ チ 何だ 今のは !
What's going on out there?
外で一体何が起き亡るんだ ! ?
I don't know.
分力`りません
All communications have been cut off.
外部との連絡が全亡断たれま した !
Damn it...
あ... 馬鹿な〟.
Impossible!
父親ふんつ うう… う・
少年ああつ お父さん!
Dad!
もう大丈夫だ さ つ力`まれ一
We're okay now.
Grab on to me.
That's the way.
そうだ 頑張れ一
Good job.
よし いいぞ
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿し ド ー  何だ ?
What is this?
There are survivors?
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しドー
まだ生き残りがいるじゃね一力ヽ
Ship, failed to kill all.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿し ド 5  船 殺し損ねた
Then we kill.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しド3殺萱
That is good.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しド4 いいと思うよ
Get away now!
イアイアン今のうちに逃げろ!
父親 うわあ !
ハツ一
You think I don't sense your thirst for blood?
そんな殺気に
気付力ヽぬと思う力ヽ?
ア 卜三ツク師匠につい亡き亡
I accompanied Master Atomic
and was waiting for the
S-class hero meeting to end,
S級集会が終わるまで
待機していたら
only to meet thunder and destruction.
と崩壊
Is this your doing?!
お前らの仕業力`
そ・ 損壊率99. 8%だと ?一
Destruction levels at 99.8%?
City A was destroyed in an instant!
一且舜でA市力ヾ
この田〕力ヾ破壊された
Who could have known her prediction
would come true this soon?!
まさ力ヽ今曹ぐ予言の時が来るなんて
誰が信じられる!
Hey! Why was this building spared?
おい !
この建物はなぜ無事なんじや !
この本部はメタ丿しナイ卜に
建設を依頼しました
We assigned Metal Knight
to construct this building.
That's why it's stronger
than the average shelter.
なので並のシェル夕一よりも
強固にできていま曹!
So that's why there are no windows.
道理で窓もねえわけだ
We should go outside and see.
とりあえず外に出亡確認し亡みなきゃ
予言のヤツ力ヽどう力ヽ判断できない
To be sure it's the prophecy.
先生 ! 外に行きま…
Master! Will you—
先生‥.
Master...
That's big!
サイ夕マでつ力`! 宇宙人力`?一
Are they aliens?
So that's what blew the city to pieces.
今ので市をコナゴナにしたの力`
Go back to...
星に帰れ !
your planet!
イアイアンハア ハア…
A militant creature.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しドー
好戦的な生き物だな
Also cautious.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿し ド 2  警戒心も強いな
Hurry. Let us hurry and kill.
早 早殺そう
いいと思うよ
That is good.
Can it be killed?
イアイアン
不死身力ヽ こいつは>一
何という殺傷能力 ! 一
Each of its strikes is lethal!
I can't beat this thing...
俺では倒せん!?
Such a weak species.
何だ 弱小種族かよ
Easily killed.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しド3殺萱の簡単
That is good.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しド4 いいと思うよ
It's splitting?
イアイアン 分裂? 一
Damn, not now...
クソ こんなところで
I will dispose of this. You handle the rest.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しドー
こいつは俺が殺しとく力ヽら
他を任せる
Very well.
分力`つた
I will go kill those that ran.
俺 さつき逃げた奴
殺しに行<
いいと思うよ
That is good.
I—
ハツ 師匠 !
Master!
イアイ 無事だつた力`?
Iairon, you okay?
You know, your left arm...
お前 左腕…
Master! Swords have no effect on this monster.
師匠 !
この怪人は剣撃の効果が薄い !
Forget me! Retreat!
俺に構わず 一旦退避を !
うおお! `
ア卜三ック侍邪麿だ!
Outta my way!
Iai! The path of the sword
does not end for you yet!
イアイ お前の剣の道は
まだ終わらせんぞ!
Stop bleeding!
止血だ !
は はい 師匠!
Yes, Master!
ヴフフ この星に
俺と戦える生命体がいた力ヽ!
So there is a life-form
on this planet that can fight.
いいだろう
我々の侵攻に抵抗してみろ!
Excellent!
Try to withstand our invasion!
星だと?
お前 宇宙力ヽら来たの力ヽ?
Planet, eh?
You from outer space?
空のオモチャには
伸間が乗つているの力ヽ?一
And you got friends up in that floaty toy?
なるほど
Yeah, that's it.
この田〕をこんな有様にしたのは
お前個人の力じゃなさそうだな
I doubt you alone have the power
to do all this to the city.
Atomic Samurai, count us in.
ア 卜三ツク侍 手伝うぜ
You the bastard that smashed this town?!
テメ一がこの田〕やつたのか コラ !
ヴフフ だつたら何だと言うんだ?
And if I am?
For all the beautiful men you killed...
ぷりぷりプリズナ一
殺された男子たちの恨みは一
I claim vengeance!
俺が晴 ら 萱 !
と一う!
Each separate attack must be
delivered with intent to kill!
ぷりぷりプリズナ一
<相手を確実に仕留めるよう
一発一発殺意をもつ亡>一
打つ‥
ダ一ク渋工ンジ工ル渋ラ一ツシユ !
Dark Angel Flash!
Issue an evacuation warning
to City A and all neighboring cities.
A市ならびに周辺都市に
避難警報を出曹んだ 急げ!
Right now!
And expand the System M
vitals monitor to cover all of City A.
ヒゲ職員それ力ヽらMシステムの
バイタ丿しモ二タ範囲を一
A市全域に拡大し
生存者の正確な数を調ベるんだ!
We need an accurate count of the survivors.
What's the threat level?
災害レベルは?
"Dragon," without doubt.
メガネ職員 竜は確実だ
No...
This might be "God."
神もあり得る
地上の敵はS級の4人がいれば
十分だろう
Four S-class heroes should be enough
to take care of the enemy on the ground.
問題は あれだよね一
The problem is that.
We can't reach it.
上空じや手が出せない一
Any aircraft would be shot down in seconds.
乗り物を用意しても
一且舜で撃ち落とされるだろうね
King, you're one of the top fighters in Class S.
キングさん
S級でも卜ツプの実力だと言われ亡いる
あなたの意見が聞きたいな
Give us your take.
King, rank 7, Class S.
ジ工ノス S級7位のキング_
Said to be the strongest man on Earth,
地上最強の男だと
囁尊されている力ヾ>一
and I see he is well respected by the other heroes…
他のヒ一ロ一力ヽらも
一目置力ヽれ亡いるの力ヽ…>
There's nothing I can do.
キング俺は何もできん
It's too high in the sky.
キングあんな上空に構えられたのでは
攻撃曹る手段がない
There's no way to attack it.
謎の飛行物体は
現在 沈黙している
But the mysterious craft is currently dormant.
We should use this opportunity
to call in Metal Knight.
今のうちに
メタ丿しナイ卜を呼ぶのがいいだろう
What the heck?! That's pathetic!
何よ それ!? 情けないわね
Aren't you supposed to be the strongest man?
あんた それでも最強の男なの?
Hey, Tornado.
ちよつ 夕ツマキちやん
If you piss King off, he'll kill you.
This city's been blown away,
and you're just going to give them a free hand?
キングを怒らせると殺されるぞ
夕ツマキ曹でに田〕力ヾー 個な<なつてるのに
また向こうに先手を譲るつもり?
信じらんない!
Unbelievable!
キングの鼓動
Well forget it! I'll take care of this myself.
もういい !
私力ヾー 人で片付けるわよ !
Wait, I will go too.
ジ工 ノ ス 待亡 俺も行
I do not know how effective I can be,
有効力`どう力`分力`らないが
but I will attack from the ground.
俺も地上力`ら攻撃してみよう
Maybe you didn't hear me.
聞こえな力ヽつたの?
もういいって言つてるでしょ !
I said forget about it!
お 落ち着んだ ジ工ノスん
Take it easy, Genos.
I understand how you feel,
but if you piss her off, she'll kill you.
気持ちは分かるが
彼女を怒らせると殺される
Very well...
ジ工ノス まあ いい一
S級どもと馴れ合う必要はない_
There is no need to team up anyway.
Master has already boarded the enemy ship.
<敵の船には
すでに先生が殴り込みに行っている>一
<これ力ヾ予言だろうと何だろうと
先生に倒せぬ悪などない>一
Whether this is the prophecy or not,
there's not a single evil Master cannot defeat.
If such an evil existed,
もし先生でも勝てない悪が
存在したなら>一
then I assume the human race
would have perished long ago.
人類など
とつ<に滅んでいるだろう>
グ口 リバ一ス ふはははは…一
Well done making it this far, intruder!
よぞここまで来たな 侵入者 ! 一
But this is the end.
だが ここまでだ
You see, there is no way
you can defeat me, Groribas!
このグロリバ一スを倒曹ことなど
不可能なのだ力ヽらな!
オレ様のアシッ ドブレスで
溶けてなくなるがいい!
My Acid Breath will melt you away!
ぐおつ!
そろそろボスが出てきても
いい頃だろ
Isn't it about time the boss showed up?
Well, if he's alive...
まだ生きてたらだけど…
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Next
Time
The
Dominator
of the
Universe
グ口リバ一スぐわはは 今回の予告は
オレ様 グ口リバ一スだ一
I, Groribas, control this preview!
I perfected some new moves.
Now I have like twenty!
オレは最近また新技が増えて
全2。種類になつたんだが一
But I couldn't show them off,
今回 全亡を見せられな力ヽつたのが
残念だ一
because, you know, they killed me off first!
その前に俺が死んじまつ た力`らな一
Lまあ・‥
が は は は は !
Next time on One-Punch Man episode eleven,
次回 ワンパンマン
第ーー話 『全宇宙の覇者』 一
"The Dominator of the Universe."
It's your fight now, Lord Boros!
お願いしま萱よ ボ口ス様